<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Services on DigitalizeIT GmbH</title>
    <link>https://digitalizeit.io/services/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Services on DigitalizeIT GmbH</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>DigitalizeIT GmbH</copyright><atom:link href="https://digitalizeit.io/services/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Blockchain Trainings</title>
      <link>https://digitalizeit.io/services/blockchaintrainings/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://digitalizeit.io/services/blockchaintrainings/</guid>
      <description>Our trainings includes blockchain introduction, business use-case evaluation and smart contract developer courses.
Introduction courses:
 History of money and what is value Bitcoin whitepaper study Blockchain fundamental techniques Wallet and private key handling  Business courses:
 Differences between public and private blockchains (public and private blockchains ) Smart contract overview Blockchain industry use-cases analysis Private blockchain governance Limitations and possibilities  Ethereum Developer courses:
 Ethereum and smart contract fundamentals Solidity programming language Develop, test and deploy smart contracts DApp development (frontend + smart contract)  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Java Software Engineering</title>
      <link>https://digitalizeit.io/services/softwareengineering/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://digitalizeit.io/services/softwareengineering/</guid>
      <description>We have 20+ years of professional software engineering experience. We have implemented solutions for the telecom, finance, transport and government sector.
 Professional expertise in Java Expertise in Python, JavaScript, Bash and more SQL and NoSQL experience We support you with full stack hands on power Building monitoring services  We are certified as “Oracle Certified Professional, Java SE 7 Programmer” as well as “Scrum Master” and “Scrum Developer”.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Smart Contract Development</title>
      <link>https://digitalizeit.io/services/smartcontract/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://digitalizeit.io/services/smartcontract/</guid>
      <description>Development of customized Ethereum smart contracts and DApps (decentralized applications).
We have three years of experience in Ethereum smart contract development. We delivered various customer projects especial in the field of tokenization. We developed ERC20 / fungible and ERC721 / non-fungible-tokens and decentralized exchange smart contracts. Furthermore we delivered for our customers customized private permissioned Ethereum networks.
We provide customized smart contracts and frontend development for our customers. We offer services to support the customer&amp;rsquo;s development team during the blockchain implementation phase.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Software Architecture</title>
      <link>https://digitalizeit.io/services/softwarearchitecture/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://digitalizeit.io/services/softwarearchitecture/</guid>
      <description>We design the overall software architecture based on the requirements and the customers expectation. Taking into account the functional and nonfunctional requirements and have in mind the whole DevOps lifecycle.
 We are doing software architecture and integration architecture. Based on your idea and business case, we design the software architecture. Focusing on cloud and serverless infrastructure. Focusing on automation, scaling and security best practices.  </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
