<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Dienstleistungen on DigitalizeIT GmbH</title>
    <link>https://digitalizeit-gmbh.github.io/de/services/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Dienstleistungen on DigitalizeIT GmbH</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language><atom:link href="https://digitalizeit-gmbh.github.io/de/services/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://digitalizeit-gmbh.github.io/de/services/blockchain/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://digitalizeit-gmbh.github.io/de/services/blockchain/</guid>
      <description>Blockchain &amp;amp; crypto Advisory We have several years professional experience on consulting and designing blockchain solutions for the industry.
 We support you with blockchain cryptocurrency advisory services. Business case shaping. Solution design and technology advisory.  We have delivered solutions to the pharma, banking and commodity trading industries. We have built supply-chain, identity, tokenization and trading services PoCs and MvPs.
The unique properties of the blockchain technology opens a new range of businesses and revenue models.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://digitalizeit-gmbh.github.io/de/services/smartcontract/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://digitalizeit-gmbh.github.io/de/services/smartcontract/</guid>
      <description>Smart Contract and DApp Development Development of customized Ethereum smart contracts and DApps (decentralized applications).
We have three years of experience in Ethereum smart contract development. We delivered various customer projects especial in the field of tokenization. We developed ERC20 / fungible and ERC721 / non-fungible-tokens and decentralized exchange smart contracts. Furthermore we delivered for our customers customized private permissioned Ethereum networks.
We provide customized smart contracts and frontend development for our customers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://digitalizeit-gmbh.github.io/de/services/trainings/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://digitalizeit-gmbh.github.io/de/services/trainings/</guid>
      <description>Blockchain Trainings Our trainings includes blockchain introduction, business use-case evaluation and smart contract developer courses.
Introduction courses:
 History of money and what is value Bitcoin whitepaper study Blockchain fundamental techniques Wallet and private key handling  Business courses:
 Differences between public and private blockchains (public and private blockchains ) Smart contract overview Blockchain industry use-cases analysis Private blockchain governance Limitations and possibilities  Ethereum Developer courses:
 Ethereum and smart contract fundamentals Solidity programming language Develop, test and deploy smart contracts DApp development (frontend + smart contract)  </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
